Kryptic is a horror, thriller, drama film directed by Kourtney Roy.
A woman’s search for a missing cryptzoologist leads to her
own riveting cosmic quest for identity.
Kay, played by Chloe Pirrie.
Morgan, played by Jeff Gladstone.
Caleb, played by Jason Deline.
Sasha, played by Ali Rusu-Tahir.
Sarah, played by Kamantha Naidoo.
Betty, played by Jenna Hill.
Kryptic is a Canadian horror thriller film, directed
by Kourtney Roy and released in 2024.
The film stars Chloe Pirrie in a dual role as Barb Valentine, a cryptid hunter who has disappeared while hunting for the Sooka, a mysterious forest creature, and Kay, a woman who herself encounters
the Sooka while searching for Barb, and abandons her life to embark on a new quest for meaning and identity after the encounter eliminates all her memories of who she used to be.
The cast also includes Jeff Gladstone, Jason Deline, Ali Rusu-Tahir,
Kamantha Naidoo, Jenna Hill, Pam Kearns, Jane Stanton, Sara J.
Southey, Jennifer Copping, Moses Wamukoya, Sarah Hayward,
Patti Allan, Christina Lewall and Ardy Ramezani.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.